http://www.cueblocks.com/privacy-policy/

PRIVACY POLICYThank you for visiting the CueBlocks website!!If you use the CueBlocks website, you are accepting the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with the Privacy Policy, you must discontinue use of this website.From time to time we may modify our security and website procedures without notice.We are committed to preserving the confidentiality of the personal information we receive about you. The following information is provided to help you understand how we gather, use and protect personal information.The Information We CollectYou typically provide personal information when communicating with us or other persons, in writing, by phone or electronically. Examples of this information include:Name Company name Address Email Id. Phone number Web address Descriptions of business issuesThe Way We Use InformationWe use the information you provide about yourself and your business to reply to your enquiries.We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties.We use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website. For example, we track how frequently individual pages are visited as an indicator of interest levels in different service areas.We use aggregate data obtained through our free tools to research and compare search engines.We use security measures reasonably designed to protect the information we obtain about you. These include: Third parties performing services for us and having access to your information are required to maintain the confidentiality of the information.We restrict access to your information in our own offices to specific individuals who have a need to use that information in connection with their employment, and those individuals are subject to an internal confidentiality policy.Information about the CueBlocks Web SiteIn general, you may visit our website without telling us who you are or revealing any personally identifiable information about yourself. Our servers do, however, collect a variety of technical data, which we store in aggregate form. This data includes (but is not limited to) your IP address (a unique number that identifies your access account on the Internet), domain, and web browser information. We may track the page you visited before coming to CueBlocks.com, the page you link to when you leave CueBlocks.com, which of our pages you access, and how long you spend on each page. We use this information to assess site usage, and to help us make improvements to its design and content.CueBlocks uses Traffic Log Analyzers to analyze traffic to this site.At times, we conduct on–line surveys to better understand the needs and profile of our visitors. When we conduct a survey, we will let you know how we will use the information at the time of its collection.SecurityThis site has implemented security measures to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. While we believe these measures to be sufficient, due to the nature of the Internet, we cannot guarantee that no unauthorized access to our servers will occur.LinksOur website may contain links to other sites on the Internet. Please remember when you click on one of those links you are leaving the CueBlocks website and entering another website. We are not responsible for the security, privacy practices, or content of these other websites. If you click on a third party link, the privacy policies of that website will govern the use of your information by that website´s operator. We assume no responsibility or liability for the actions of such third parties with respect to their use of your information or otherwise.CookiesA "cookie" is a small piece of information placed on your computer by the website you are visiting online. It allows the site to recognize your computer during the session, or when you visit the site again.CueBlocks uses temporary cookies, which store a session identifier to facilitate the consumer´s use of the website. We will not collect any information from your computer or leave any retrievable information on your computer using this type of cookie.Choice/Opt–OutCueBlocks.com provides all users with the opportunity to modify or opt–out of receiving non–essential (promotional, marketing–related) communications from us on behalf of our partners, and from us in general, after subscribing to our Newsletter.Sharing of InformationWe may disclose personal information if permitted to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such disclosure is reasonably necessary to respond to subpoenas, court orders, or other legal process.We may also share some or all of your personal information with:Law enforcement offices, third party rights owners, or others in the good faith belief that such disclosure is reasonably necessary to: enforce our Terms of Use or Privacy Policy; respond to claims that an advertisement, posting or other content violates the rights of a third party; or protect the rights, property or personal safety of our users or the general public.Another business entity should we (or our assets) plan to merge with, or be acquired by that business entity. Should such a transaction occur, that other business entity (or the new combined entity) will be required to follow this privacy policy with respect to your personal information.Enquiries and requests relating to this information should be sent by E–mail to webmaster@cueblocks.com or to our mailing address:Cue Blocks Technologies Pvt. Ltd. SCO 822, Second Floor NAC ManiMajra Chandigarh India – 160101 Phone: +91–172–2739754A Word From Our Clients
PreviousOur experience in outsourcing services has been the most pleasurable and overwhelmingly successful since our involvement with CueBlocks Team.Warren Wise -
DirectorCueBlocks never cease to amaze me with their infinite knowledge and understanding of every corner of the online sphere.Fiona -
Founder & CEO Their technical experience supporting and improving our Magento websites has allowed us to grow considerably as an organization.Nick Pullano -
CEO CueBlocks is a world-class team located in a small town. It is impressive to see the caliber of the team and the business practices they follow.Manisha Lath Gupta -
Co-Founder & CEOI have been greatly impressed by their reliability, communication, attention to detail, and most importantly, the high quality of work that they produce for us on a daily basis.Dave Anderson -
Co-OwnerOur experience in outsourcing services has been the most pleasurable and overwhelmingly successful since our involvement with CueBlocks Team.Warren Wise -
DirectorCueBlocks never cease to amaze me with their infinite knowledge and understanding of every corner of the online sphere.Fiona -
Founder & CEO Their technical experience supporting and improving our Magento websites has allowed us to grow considerably as an organization.Nick Pullano -
CEO CueBlocks is a world-class team located in a small town. It is impressive to see the caliber of the team and the business practices they follow.Manisha Lath Gupta -
Co-Founder & CEOI have been greatly impressed by their reliability, communication, attention to detail, and most importantly, the high quality of work that they produce for us on a daily basis.Dave Anderson -
Co-OwnerOur experience in outsourcing services has been the most pleasurable and overwhelmingly successful since our involvement with CueBlocks Team.Warren Wise -
Director NextSatisfied clients are the fuel that keeps us on the road to learning, improving, growing, and evolving. Check out what our clients have to say about their association with CueBlocks on Clutch.
